const level3Questions = [
    
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 17?",
            options: ["19", "22", "21", "20"],
            answer: "20"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 93?",
            options: ["97", "98", "96", "95"],
            answer: "96"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 41?",
            options: ["43", "46", "45", "44"],
            answer: "44"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 72?",
            options: ["74", "77", "76", "75"],
            answer: "75"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 3?",
            options: ["5", "8", "7", "6"],
            answer: "6"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 56?",
            options: ["58", "61", "59", "60"],
            answer: "59"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 28?",
            options: ["30", "33", "32", "31"],
            answer: "31"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 85?",
            options: ["87", "90", "89", "88"],
            answer: "88"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 10?",
            options: ["12", "15", "14", "13"],
            answer: "13"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 49?",
            options: ["51", "54", "53", "52"],
            answer: "52"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 64?",
            options: ["66", "69", "68", "67"],
            answer: "67"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 2?",
            options: ["4", "7", "6", "5"],
            answer: "5"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 98?",
            options: ["100", "103", "102", "101"],
            answer: "101"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 37?",
            options: ["39", "42", "41", "40"],
            answer: "40"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 7?",
            options: ["9", "12", "11", "10"],
            answer: "10"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 20?",
            options: ["22", "25", "24", "23"],
            answer: "23"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 79?",
            options: ["81", "84", "83", "82"],
            answer: "82"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 61?",
            options: ["63", "66", "64", "65"],
            answer: "64"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 16?",
            options: ["18", "21", "20", "19"],
            answer: "19"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 95?",
            options: ["97", "100", "99", "98"],
            answer: "98"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 87?",
            options: ["89", "92", "91", "90"],
            answer: "90"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 1?",
            options: ["3", "6", "5", "4"],
            answer: "4"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 68?",
            options: ["70", "73", "72", "71"],
            answer: "71"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 32?",
            options: ["34", "37", "36", "35"],
            answer: "35"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 52?",
            options: ["54", "57", "56", "55"],
            answer: "55"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 96?",
            options: ["98", "101", "100", "99"],
            answer: "99"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 9?",
            options: ["11", "14", "13", "12"],
            answer: "12"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 44?",
            options: ["46", "49", "48", "47"],
            answer: "47"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 71?",
            options: ["73", "76", "75", "74"],
            answer: "74"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 53?",
            options: ["55", "58", "57", "56"],
            answer: "56"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 39?",
            options: ["41", "44", "43", "42"],
            answer: "42"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 23?",
            options: ["25", "28", "27", "26"],
            answer: "26"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 5?",
            options: ["7", "10", "9", "8"],
            answer: "8"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 83?",
            options: ["85", "88", "87", "86"],
            answer: "86"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 65?",
            options: ["67", "70", "69", "68"],
            answer: "68"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 76?",
            options: ["78", "81", "80", "79"],
            answer: "79"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 35?",
            options: ["37", "40", "39", "38"],
            answer: "38"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 14?",
            options: ["16", "19", "18", "17"],
            answer: "17"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 25?",
            options: ["27", "30", "29", "28"],
            answer: "28"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 70?",
            options: ["72", "75", "74", "73"],
            answer: "73"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 31?",
            options: ["33", "36", "35", "34"],
           
    
     answer: "34"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 86?",
            options: ["88", "91", "90", "89"],
            answer: "89"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 60?",
            options: ["62", "65", "63", "64"],
            answer: "63"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 78?",
            options: ["80", "83", "82", "81"],
            answer: "81"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 13?",
            options: ["15", "18", "17", "16"],
            answer: "16"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 58?",
            options: ["60", "63", "61", "62"],
            answer: "61"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 21?",
            options: ["23", "26", "25", "24"],
            answer: "24"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 81?",
            options: ["83", "86", "85", "84"],
            answer: "84"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 45?",
            options: ["47", "50", "49", "48"],
            answer: "48"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 6?",
            options: ["8", "11", "10", "9"],
            answer: "9"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 11?",
            options: ["13", "16", "15", "14"],
            answer: "14"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 48?",
            options: ["50", "53", "52", "51"],
            answer: "51"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 80?",
            options: ["82", "85", "84", "83"],
            answer: "83"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 19?",
            options: ["21", "24", "23", "22"],
            answer: "22"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 97?",
            options: ["99", "102", "101", "100"],
            answer: "100"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 69?",
            options: ["71", "74", "73", "72"],
            answer: "72"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 24?",
            options: ["26", "29", "28", "27"],
            answer: "27"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 74?",
            options: ["76", "79", "78", "77"],
            answer: "77"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 54?",
            options: ["56", "59", "58", "57"],
            answer: "57"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 67?",
            options: ["69", "72", "71", "70"],
            answer: "70"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 38?",
            options: ["40", "43", "42", "41"],
            answer: "41"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 18?",
            options: ["20", "23", "22", "21"],
            answer: "21"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 8?",
            options: ["10", "13", "12", "11"],
            answer: "11"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 62?",
            options: ["64", "67", "66", "65"],
            answer: "65"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 29?",
            options: ["31", "34", "33", "32"],
            answer: "32"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 50?",
            options: ["52", "55", "54", "53"],
            answer: "53"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 12?",
            options: ["14", "17", "16", "15"],
            answer: "15"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 59?",
            options: ["61", "64", "63", "62"],
            answer: "62"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 89?",
            options: ["91", "94", "93", "92"],
            answer: "92"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 27?",
            options: ["29", "32", "31", "30"],
            answer: "30"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 36?",
            options: ["38", "41", "40", "39"],
            answer: "39"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 84?",
            options: ["86", "89", "88", "87"],
            answer: "87"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 75?",
            options: ["77", "80", "79", "78"],
            answer: "78"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 55?",
            options: ["57", "60", "59", "58"],
            answer: "58"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 0?",
            options: ["2", "5", "4", "3"],
            answer: "3"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 63?",
            options: ["65", "68", "67", "66"],
            answer: "66"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 47?",
            options: ["49", "52", "51", "50"],
            answer: "50"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 99?",
            options: ["101", "104", "103", "102"],
            answer: "102"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 73?",
            options: ["75", "78", "77", "76"],
            answer: "76"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 91?",
            options: ["93", "96", "95", "94"],
            answer: "94"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 43?",
            options: ["45", "48", "47", "46"],
            answer: "46"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 30?",
            options: ["32", "35", "34", "33"],
            answer: "33"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 15?",
            options: ["17", "20", "19", "18"],
            answer: "18"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 51?",
            options: ["53", "56", "55", "54"],
            answer: "54"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 94?",
            options: ["96", "99", "98", "97"],
            answer: "97"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 22?",
            options: ["24", "27", "26", "25"],
            answer: "25"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 57?",
            options: ["59", "62", "61", "60"],
            answer: "60"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 46?",
            options: ["48", "51", "50", "49"],
            answer: "49"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 90?",
            options: ["92", "95", "94", "93"],
            answer: "93"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 26?",
            options: ["28", "31", "30", "29"],
            answer: "29"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 82?",
            options: ["84", "87", "86", "85"],
            answer: "85"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 4?",
            options: ["6", "9", "8", "7"],
            answer: "7"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 40?",
            options: ["42", "45", "44", "43"],
            answer: "43"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 88?",
            options: ["90", "93", "92", "91"],
            answer: "91"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 66?",
            options: ["68", "71", "70", "69"],
            answer: "69"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 42?",
            options: ["44", "47", "46", "45"],
            answer: "45"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 77?",
            options: ["79", "82", "81", "80"],
            answer: "80"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 92?",
            options: ["94", "97", "96", "95"],
            answer: "95"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 34?",
            options: ["36", "39", "38", "37"],
            answer: "37"
        },
        {
            question: "Add +3 to: 33?",
            options: ["35", "38", "37", "36"],
            answer: "36"
        }
    
  ];
  
  export default level3Questions;
  